Records of the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia; Law, Appellate, and Criminal Records; Case Papers 1802-1863
Center for Digital Research in the Humanities University of Nebraska–Lincoln
- January, Civil Trials, 89-386, 1858 (Box 853)
- January, Civil Trials, 387-648, 1858 (Box 854)
- January, Civil Trials, 651-796, 1858 (Box 855)
- January, Civil Trials, 799-941, 1858 (Box 856)
- January, Civil Trials, 943-1098, 1858 (Box 857)
- January, Civil Trials, 1099-1247, 1858 (Box 858)
- January, Civil Trials, 1249-1408, Rough Bundle, 1858 (Box 859)
- January, Judicials, 1-135, 1858 (Box 860)
- January, Judicials, 136-288, 1858 (Box 861)
- January, Judicials, 290-367, Appeals, Titlings, 1858 (Box 862)
- May, Civil Appearances, 1-176, 1858 (Box 863)
- May, Civil Appearances, 182-411, 1858 (Box 864)
- May, Civil Appearances, 417-782, Civil Trials, 3-91, 1858 (Box 865)
- May, Civil Trials, 97-404, 1858 (Box 866)
- May, Civil Trials, 406-648, 1858 (Box 867)
- May, Civil Trials, 651-804, 1858 (Box 868)
- May, Civil Trials, 818-1034, 1858 (Box 869)
- May, Judicials, 1-154, 1858 (Box 870)
- May, Judicials, 166-310, 1858 (Box 871)
- May, Judicials, 311-457, 1858 (Box 872)
- May, Appeals, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1858 (Box 873)
- October, Civil Appearances, 5-218, 1858 (Box 874)
- October, Civil Appearances, 220-441, 1858 (Box 875)
- October, Civil Appearances, 449-994, 1858 (Box 876)
- October, Civil Trials, 1-299, 1858 (Box 877)
- October, Civil Trials, 300-563, 1858 (Box 878)
- October, Civil Trials, 565-710, 1858 (Box 879)
- October, Civil Trials, 717-864, 1858 (Box 880)
- October, Civil Trials, 867-1002, Rough Bundle, 1858 (Box 881)
- October, Judicials, 1-150, 1858 (Box 882)
- October, Judicials, 151-281, 1858 (Box 883)
- October, Judicials, 283-431, 1858 (Box 884)
- October, Appeals, Titlings, 1858 (Box 885)
- January, Civil Appearances, 1-164, 1859 (Box 886)
- January, Civil Appearances, 166-369, 1859 (Box 887)
- January, Civil Appearances, 376-603, Civil Trials, 8-126, 1859 (Box 888)
- January, Civil Trials, 137-484, 1859 (Box 889)
- January, Civil Trials, 491-647, 1859 (Box 890)
- January, Civil Trials, 649-795, 1859 (Box 891)
- January, Civil Trials, 797-932, 1859 (Box 892)
- January, Civil Trials, 934-1100, Rough Bundle, 1859 (Box 893)
- January, Judicials, 1-190, 1859 (Box 894)
- January, Judicials, 191-292, Appeals, Titlings, 1859 (Box 895)
- May, Civil Appearances, 4-163, 1859 (Box 896)
- May, Civil Appearances, 165-388, 1859 (Box 897)
- May, Civil Appearances, 392-700, Civil Trials, 4-185, 1859 (Box 898)
- May, Civil Trials, 189-542, 1859 (Box 899)
- May, Civil Trials, 546-698, 1859 (Box 900)
- May, Civil Trials, 700-815, Appeals, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1859 (Box 901)
- May, Judicials, 1-160, 1859 (Box 902)
- May, Judicials, 162-324, 1859 (Box 903)
- October, Civil Appearances, 3-146, 1859 (Box 904)
- October, Civil Appearances, 150-417, 1859 (Box 905)
- October, Civil Appearances, 418-819, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1859 (Box 906)
- October, Civil Trials, 1-261, 1859 (Box 907)
- October, Civil Trials, 262-539, 1859 (Box 908)
- October, Civil Trials, 540-702, 1859 (Box 909)
- October, Civil Trials, 704-836, 1859 (Box 910)
- October, Judicials, 1-147, 1859 (Box 911)
- October, Judicials, 152-300, 1859 (Box 912)
- January, Civil Appearances, 1-150, 1860 (Box 913)
- January, Civil Appearances, 151-379, 1860 (Box 914)
- January, Civil Appearances, 393-610, Civil Trials, 7-184, 1860 (Box 915)
- January, Civil Trials, 188-462, 1860 (Box 916)
- January, Civil Trials, 465-616, 1860 (Box 917)
- January, Civil Trials, 618-756, 1860 (Box 918)
- January, Civil Trials, 760-911, 1860 (Box 919)
- January, Judicials, 1-100, 1860 (Box 920)
- January, Judicials, 100-161, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1860 (Box 921)
- May, Civil Appearances, 1-139, 1860 (Box 922)
- May, Civil Appearances, 141-317, 1860 (Box 923)
- May, Civil Appearances, 318-712, Appeals, 1860 (Box 924)
- May, Civil Trials, 1-282, 1860 (Box 925)
- May, Civil Trials, 286-504, 1860 (Box 926)
- May, Civil Trials, 509-650, 1860 (Box 927)
- May, Civil Trials, 654-731, Judicials, 1-44, 1860 (Box 928)
- May, Judicials, 45-183, 1860 (Box 929)
- May, Judicials, 186-308, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1860 (Box 930)
- October, Civil Appearances, 1-155, 1860 (Box 931)
- October, Civil Appearances, 157-463, 1860 (Box 932)
- October, Civil Appearances, 464-737, Civil Trials, 1-121, 1860 (Box 933)
- October, Civil Trials, 129-379, 1860 (Box 934)
- October, Civil Trials, 382-511, 1860 (Box 935)
- October, Civil Trials, 513-637, 1860 (Box 936)
- October, Civil Trials, 639-760, Rough Bundle, 1860 (Box 937)
- October, Appeals, Judicials, 1-110, 1860 (Box 938)
- October, Judicials, 111-226, Titlings, 1860 (Box 939)
- January, Civil Appearances, 10-200, 1861 (Box 940)
- January, Civil Appearances, 202-547, 1861 (Box 941)
- January, Civil Appearances, 549-679, Civil Trials, 14-255, 1861 (Box 942)
- January, Civil Trials, 258-451, 1861 (Box 943)
- January, Civil Trials, 452-571, 1861 (Box 944)
- January, Civil Trials, 573-701, 1861 (Box 945)
- January, Civil Trials, 703-774, Appeals, 1861 (Box 946)
- January, Judicials, 1-120, 1861 (Box 947)
- January, Judicials, 121-219, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1861 (Box 948)
- May, Civil Appearances, 1-200, 1861 (Box 949)
- May, Civil Appearances, 202-611, 1861 (Box 950)
- May, Civil Trials, 181-788, Rough Bundle, Titlings, 1861 (Box 951)
- May, Judicials, 1-136, 1861 (Box 952)
- May, Judicials, 138-249, 1861 (Box 953)
- October, Civil Appearances, 2-167, 1861 (Box 954)
- October, Civil Appearances, 168-493, 1861 (Box 955)
- October, Civil Appearances, 508-941, Rough Bundle, 1861 (Box 956)
- October, Civil Trials, 25-391, 1861 (Box 957)
- October, Civil Trials, 393-547, 1861 (Box 958)
- October, Civil Trials, 550-674, 1861 (Box 959)
- October, Civil Trials, 676-813, 1861 (Box 960)
- October, Civil Trials, 816-960, 1861 (Box 961)
- October, Civil Trials, 962-1103, 1861 (Box 962)
- October, Appeals, Judicials, Titlings, 1861 (Box 963)
- January, Civil Appearances, 3-225, 1862 (Box 964)
- January, Civil Appearances, 226-393, 1862 (Box 965)
- January, Civil Appearances, 409-663, Appeals, 1862 (Box 966)
- January, Civil Trials, 5-199, 1862 (Box 967)
- January, Civil Trials, 211-499, 1862 (Box 968)
- January, Civil Trials, 503-653, 1862 (Box 969)
- January, Civil Trials, 655-769, 1862 (Box 970)
- January, Civil Trials, 771-871, 1862 (Box 971)
- January, Civil Trials, 873-1003, 1862 (Box 972)
- January, Civil Trials, 1005-1110, Rough Bundle, 1862 (Box 973)
- January, Judicials, 1-148, 1862 (Box 974)
- January, Judicials, 150-240, 1862 (Box 975)
- January, Judicials, 241-327, Titlings, 1862 (Box 976)